{
    "10": {
        "answer": "wichtig",
        "e-factor": 0.5600000000000004,
        "question": "important",
        "i-interval": 1
    },
    "1": {
        "answer": "ganz",
        "e-factor": 2.8000000000000003,
        "question": "whole, all the",
        "i-interval": 1
    },
    "3": {
        "answer": "gro\u00df",
        "e-factor": 2.66,
        "question": "big, large, great",
        "i-interval": 1
    },
    "2": {
        "answer": "m\u00f6glich",
        "e-factor": 2.5,
        "question": "possible",
        "i-interval": 1
    },
    "5": {
        "answer": "gut",
        "e-factor": 2.6,
        "question": "good",
        "i-interval": 1
    },
    "4": {
        "answer": "eigen",
        "e-factor": 2.36,
        "question": "own",
        "i-interval": 1
    },
    "7": {
        "answer": "neu",
        "e-factor": 2.6,
        "question": "new",
        "i-interval": 1
    },
    "6": {
        "answer": "sch\u00f6n",
        "e-factor": 2.5,
        "question": "beautiful, pleasant, good",
        "i-interval": 1
    },
    "9": {
        "answer": "erste",
        "e-factor": 2.36,
        "question": "first",
        "i-interval": 1
    },
    "8": {
        "answer": "sp\u00e4t",
        "e-factor": 2.36,
        "question": "late",
        "i-interval": 1
    }
}